{
    "subject": "resource/Madame_Butterfly_(1915_film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_silent_feature_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Madame Butterfly (1915 film) is Category:American silent feature films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9751082062721252,
            "question": "Is Madame Butterfly (1915) a silent film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8477134108543396,
            "question": "What type of feature is Madame Butterfly (1915)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8221816420555115,
            "question": "What category does the film Madame Butterfly (1915) belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7693476676940918,
            "question": "Does Madame Butterfly (1915) fall under American cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7628310918807983,
            "question": "Can you name a film that shares the same category as Madame Butterfly (1915)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7016556859016418,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of American silent feature films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.68397057056427,
            "question": "How did the release of Madame Butterfly (1915) contribute to American cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.570968747138977,
            "question": "What other films from 1915 are considered significant in American cinema history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5342294573783875,
            "question": "Are there any notable directors known for making American silent feature films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.504602313041687,
            "question": "In what year was the film Madame Butterfly released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Madame Butterfly (1915 film) is Category:American silent feature films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7240_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable directors known for making American silent feature films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7240_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other films from 1915 are considered significant in American cinema history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7240_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the release of Madame Butterfly (1915) contribute to American cinema?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7240_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7240_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7240_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7240_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7240_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7240_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7240_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7240_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7240_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7240_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7240_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\nThe triple is \"Madame Butterfly (1915 film)\" as a Category: American silent feature films.\n\nAfter analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The documents indeed describe Madame Butterfly (1915) as an American silent film.\n* There are mentions of the film's country of origin, \"United States of America\" in one of the documents.\n* The film is also categorized under \"American silent feature films\" in another document.\n\nTherefore, based on the context information provided, I conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe query \"The subject of Madame Butterfly (1915 film) is Category:American silent feature films.\" can be supported by the documents, as multiple entries mention that \"Madame Butterfly\" was a silent film from the United States and fits into the category of American silent feature films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The subject of Madame Butterfly (1915 film) is not an American silent feature film, but rather a British-American co-production. The production company for the film was Famous Players Film Company, which was based in the United States, but the actual filming and direction were done by Sidney Olcott in Japan.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}